Hi.
I'm looking for a seed.
Red, small.
A little seed, this big.
Grows into a round plant,
this high...
Does it flower?
No, you can't eat it.
The plant is about this high.
Is it sold here?
I was told I could buy it here.
Where can I buy it?
It's too late.
-Ok, thanks.
Hi, I'm looking for a little red seed.
A little seed.
I don't know its name.
What?
No, that's not it. A seed.
That I'm falling?
That's why he's so fat.
During the day he barely eats.
His body goes on high alert.
When he pigs out at night
his body thinks
it needs to absorb everything.
So it's better
to eat a little at a time.
Are you listening?
Yes. All the way down?
Yes.
Know where it is?
No.
I'm hungry.
Thanks.
Why show my feelings
if we never talk?
What're they doing?
I think they're going out.
No, guys like you.
What do you mean?
I think I'll skip work tomorrow.
You always say that.
Look, I cut my finger.
That's normal.
Normal for you, not for me.
You drinking a beer?
Are you kidding? Obviously.
I can't see, but I can smell it.
You can't see?
My eyes need to adjust.
Let's play "Say it, win it!"
You lie.
What?
He's a big liar.
It's no fun playing with you.
My shoes!
-Take them off.
Let's order pizza.
It'll do us good.
Go for it.
Yep.
Cool.
I dreamt air was like dough.
What?
Bread dough.
-Raw?
And I destroyed myself
to understand.
What are you doing?
Nothing.
Say it, win it.
I thought you were making fun of me.
Why show my feelings
if we never talk?
I don't want to go.
So what's your hurry?
No other openings.
Oh well.
She's a bitch.
My shoulder hurts.
Look.
Did she do that?
Indirectly, yes.
Sure this is the way?
Vacation is no vacation
if I keep doing the same thing.
Are you listening?
Got the flowers?
Yep.
Where'd you put them?
Tell me.
Deep inside in total safety.
That way I'm sure they're safe.
Spare me the details.
Want some?
No, thanks.
What?
That you should put it in the bag.
Oh, I heard it,
you said jungle.
So, are you coming tonight ?
I don't think so,
I don't have any money.
Don't worry, I'll lend you.
No, it's ok
if I don't have, I don't have.
Hey, Archie !
What's up?
I'm good.
- Are you coming this way ?
- Yes, I'm going home.
I forgot to tell I was coming late.
- So you where with Kinny last night ?
- No ...
Ah, he texted me that they
were doing a party downstairs.
But I was already on my bed,
eating cheese, drunk,
so I didn't feel like going.
I turned off the lights, phone, everything.
I dissapeared.
I think I'm getting old.
So you're not coming tonight?
I don't think so.
I think he wants to spend time
with Alf and Bobby.
Stop lying!
I bought a new plant. It's funny.
This tree is new too, right?
-Yes.
And why is it funny?
You never know how
it'll act with you.
What's it called?
Armadillo tail.
What's it do
Makes me want
to see pictures of girls.
Girls?
-Yep.
Have you talked to Paul ?
No ...
Sorry
I've not been able to talk to Paul
because I've got no light
for some days now.
Ah, so you're still without light
- Yeah, twenty days !
- Twenty days ?
You can come to my house if you want.
-Ok.
Mabel !
- What are you doing here ?
- Hey ! Where are you going ?
- I'm going to school, you ?
-I'm going to work.
- Oh, that's nice.
- I don't know.
-You don't know what ?
- Going to work ...
Ok, come this way.
Is it this way to your school ?
No. I come here when
I don't want to go to school.
I want to know about music,
and download music.
- You want?
- No.
I'm ok.
In what could I specialize?
Maybe you could work
in a supermarket.
Yes ! I will learn
more about music there.
In what could I specialize?
Are you listening ?
Doctor, I think this guy is lying.
But it's not important.
Really?
Do we need to find
a psychiatrist for him?
Not that much.
Tell him to go out.
Please !
It's just a minute.
I've got all the papers !
I won't come again,
I swear.
Was that already here?
Is it new?
I need more money.
Soon.
I still don't believe
in reincarnation.
Ten more.
Three...
Well... five.
Sleeping in the daytime isn't sleep.
When I was little
I said "dead" for "bed".
Find the seeds?
Another time
you might fall in love with me.