Hi, and I think we should say ''goodbye''
because the filming is over.
Why?
We've just talked to our father.
He doesn't want to participate in this film anymore.
It was fine with him as long as he could tell you
exactly what to do and what to show.
He wanted to glorify himself in front of the camera
but the truth is we quarrel all the time
and we can hardly make ends meet.
So, what are you going to do with
the medical examination of your eyes?
I have no idea.
I would have to tell him that you want
to help me with it.
And, you'll tell him that.
Out of reach
I'm with Karolina now. We've been watching
some photos on the computer.
And?
Something's wrong with my eyes.
When I sit in front of the computer, I get a terrible headache.
And?
Karolina smsed Kuba yesterday and asked him
if he could help us
with arranging the medical examination of my eyes.
And?
And, he agreed but it has to be our decision.
But why are you arranging things behind my back?
Karolina wrote to him, not me.
You are really messing up things.
What do you mean?
O.K. He can help you
with the medical examination, but I don't want to have anything to do with him.
I don't want to do anything against you.
That's why I'm asking you.
Karolina wrote to him and he agreed to help,
but I want to have your permission first.
O.K. So, go and do it, but I don't want to
see him anymore. There will be no more filming!
So, you've decided to come here with your sister, right?
Yes.
You're 16. Why did't you come with your parents?
Hold this book, all right?
Now, look at it and tell me what you can see.
There are smaller signs here and bigger signs over there.
I can only see a different colour here.
All right.
I'm showing you my hand now.
How many fingers can you see?
I don't know.
And now? Can you see my hand?
I can see it now.
Can you count my fingers?
How many fingers can you see with your left eye?
I can't tell.
And now? Can you see anything?
No.
Usually, it's possible for an eye to recover provided
the problem is taken care of by the parents
because you are still a child, aren't you?
The problem, however, was ignored.
The eye wasn't attended to with sufficient care
and now it doesn't function at all.
You're now 16 and for the last 16 years
your eyesight has been deteriorating.
This means that it won't be possible for you to see
with your left eye at all.
Stop crying.
I have no plans for the future. Life is life.
You're in a shitty situation because you're only 16.
I am sure I'll leave home sooner than you.
Do you want to bet?
Sure. A hundred zloty.
There was one card. Actually, it was not a card
but a big cup made of cardstock
that we prepared for the Father's Day.
We gave it to him with a note
''for the best father in the world''.
It was the only thing that
we really wanted to prepare for him.
And, we did it out of our own will.
That's your handwriting: ''Dad, on this joyous day I wish you
good health, best of luck and may God bless you.
I want you to be happy for the next thousand years and
I hope you’ll spend this time with Mum''.
Sentence on behalf of the Republic of Poland
against Bożena Siankowska.
And, we've got the reference number.
Another reference number.
This is what we're looking for.
So, we need to borrow it from Dad.
It's enough if we copy it.
We can find her ID number at the Citizens Advice Bureau
or take it from Grandma.
Why would they give us our mother's ID number
at the Citizens Advice Bureau?
We'll just tell them that we're looking for our mother.
Come in.
Good morning.
We've got little information about our mother because
Klaudia was 2.5 and I was 3.5 years old when she left us
and we still don't know where she is.
Klaudia met our cousins who said she'd been put to jail.
We don't know if she's in Poland or abroad.
We also heard gossips that she'd been deported to Poland
and was in prison somewhere here.
We have no access to any documents.
Does she use your father’s surname or her maiden name?
No idea. After the wedding,
she used our father's name.
Actually, they didn't divorce.
It was ''annulment of marriage''.
She could have used her maiden name.
We don't know that. She was pursued by police
when the divorce case was still in court.
She didn't come to court for the marriage annulment verdict.
We just want to know if she's alive,
what's going on with her and where she is
According to the penal code, as the injured party
you have access to the court files.
I suggest you should go to court
and browse through the files
to find all the possible information about your mother.
This may help you get in touch with her.
Welcome to our sanctuary. Our alcohol den.
So, we've arrived at the place where we drink, have parties…
Where it smells.
Where we sleep, play cards, play chess…
This is not me.
This is you.
Klaudia, I remember having
a completely different outfit at that time.
I was so pretty.
Oh, yes. A real beauty. Wait a second!
Give me some of them.
You're goimg through them so slowly.
We don't have many memories of our Mum.
I don't remember what she actually looked like.
There was only one time when she came to visit us.
There are only three photos here.
She showed up once to give us the bicycles
and she was wearing this white dress.
Yes, a ''superman costume''.
It was a white, semi-transparent cloth
and she had long blond hair.
She was wearing sunglasses to hide her black eyes.
Do you remember this gold bracelet she was wearing?
Yes, rings and earrings.
Then, it turned out that she robbed a jeweller.
If I was to see Bożena again, I would…
She would tell you the same thing:
''Sweetie, I had no choice''.
I would kick her ass.
I wouldn't listen to her chattering.
I would pay her back for all the 16 years
when she wasn’t here on Mother's Day…
Nobody would be able to calm me down.
Maybe violence is not the best way out,
but kicking her ass would make me feel better.
It'd be a miracle if I didn't kill her.
Good morning.
Good morning. Come in, please.
Forty one.
Thirty four. Forty one. Here?
Aha.
Good morning. Can we come in?
Come in, please.
The father doesn't know where his wife is
although he tried to find her.
Her friends refused to inform him where she is.
The father stopped drinking two years ago.
He is a member of Alcoholics Anonymous.
He believes other members of the AA group support him.
The father seems to care for his daughters.
Bożena Siankowska has been deprived of her parental rights.
She isn't interested in her daughters and doesn't contact them.
How come her ID number is not in the files?
What do you mean?
You can change your place of residence, but not your ID number!
Whose fault is it then?
It's the court's fault.
They should have the basic data.
You always want to have everything right away.
Good morning. This is Bożena speaking.
Please leave the message.
Hi, Mum. We're having a walk with Tola now.
We need to talk about our trip.
So, call me or I'll call you later. Bye.
We've been in touch with her for only two weeks
now and she wants to meet us now?
I don't even know this woman and
I'm supposed to visit her abroad?
It's more difficult for you because
you don't even remember her.
She hasn't given us enough time
to accept the fact that she’s with us again.
She wants to buy us one-way tickets.
We can come only if we have return tickets.
If we have return tickets and more time to think it over.
Not just two weeks.
So, she called you first or what?
I called her first because I stole her phone number
from Grandma's mobile.
And, what did you tell her?
At first it was the answering machine.
Then, I gave Tola her phone number.
Tola smsed her and Bożena called her back.
After they talked, Tola was crying.
I was furious because Bożena didn't call me at all.
I texted her to tell her how bad I felt
about it and she called me back immediately.
And?
She started crying and giving excuses
for what she did in the past.
She's abandoned you and now
she suddenly wants you to visit her?
She last saw you when you were 3 and now you're 18.
Maybe she'll contact you again when you turn 30?
Aren't you afraid that after you meet her,
she'll disappear from your life again?
Aren't you going to suffer even more?
I know it's risky.
She's been in touch with everyone else but you.
She could have talked to you just for a second
to see what you're like.
She's forgotten about you
and now you want to hit the fucking road?
Just to see Paris? To see what she's like?
I don't know if I should go or not…
Don't you worry about anything.
Now you're with Dad. I'll help if I can.
I'll send you money from time to time.
If you want, you can come here in five or six months.
Karolina will come first and see what it's like here. Hello?
I'm here.
She can stay with me because I live alone.
I've got a job.
I haven't told this to Karolina, but I think
she's going through a hard time now.
I think she has my character.
You're absolutely right.
That's my impression of her. I've tried to learn from
my own mistakes and I want her to do the same.
I don't want you girls to make similar mistakes
like me and your father.
I'd like you to settle down,
but Karolina seems to be very much like me.
That's why I'd like her to come here.
Maybe I could help by telling her about
the mistakes I've made.
We haven't seen each other for such a long time.
Right.
We have a chance to change things for better.
And then, we'll see…
How will we recognize each other at the airport?
I'm 160 cm tall and I'm a blonde.
I'm slim and I weigh 48 kg.
What a starveling!
What?
So, you're quite thin. Thinner that me.
And, how much do you weigh?
52kg.
Almost my weight. How about your hair? Is it long?
Shoulder length.
I have longer hair.
Last time I saw you, you also had long hair.
Who is it?
What?
Who was it?
It's a friend of mine. He drove me home.
I've told him my children are coming over.
He'd like to say ''hello'' to you,
but you don't speak French or English.
Wait a second. I'll give him the phone
so you can tell him ''hello''.
Hello.
Fuck off.
It's my first flight. This is my reservation.
Where shall I go?
Where are you flying?
To Paris.
It's not possible to say what you're going to feel
and what she's going to feel.
I'm going to tell her to keep her hands away from me.
I wonder what she looks like.
How did she describe herself? Blond hair, 160 cm tall.
Just like me.
She described herself very precisely.
I need to go. Take care. Say ''hello'' to Kasia and her son.
We'll sms each other.
Goodbye my love.
I wonder what she looks like and how they will
get on with each other.
Karolina will need at least three days
to tell me everything about it.
What Bożena looks like, what they did, where they went.
I take care of Philip for 5 to 6 hours every day.
Witek comes to collect him after work
and then takes him to Kasia.
Would you like to have your own child in the future?
In the future, yes. And, more than one.
She hasn't seen me for several years
and now the boss won't let her pick me up.
She could have taken a short break
to collect me from the airport. Pity.
We're going to the centre of Paris now.
I hope we'll see each other  tonight or tomorrow.
She told me she didn't work on Sundays,
but then she said she did…
It's a crazy place. Millions of people, pubs,
residences, monuments. Fuck!
It's really incredible.
Tola is going to regret she hasn't come here.
It's better for me and Karolina to go separately.
Karolina has her own questions to ask and I have my own.
Bożena will have more time to talk to us
if we come separately.
If we attacked her with too many questions together,
she'd feel overwhelmed.
It could be too much of a shock for her.
So, Karolina will talk to her first
and then I'll go and ask her my questions.
I think everything should be fine.
Hello.
Hi Mum.
Hi Karolinka.
I was calling you yesterday. You didn't answer.
I left my mobile at work.
Have you read my message?
I haven't checked the messages.
They brought my phone in the morning.
I'm going to take a bath now and we'll meet later on.
Listen, I’ve got something to do now. Let’s meet at 5 o’clock by the Eiffel Tower.
O.K.
Fine. My heart's beating so hard. What?
So, 5 o'clock by the Eiffel Tower.
Right.
How do you like it here?
It's nice. A totally different world.
It seems nice to tourists, but it's different
for people who work here.
I guess so.
I can see that she misses us and really cares.
She's interested in how we live.
It looks good. Maybe not everything is perfect,
but it's a good start.
It's difficult to meet somebody who
abandoned you many years ago.
You hate this person,
but you're also somehow attracted to her.
You just feel it's the right moment to meet up,
but it’s very difficult emotionally.
My hands are trembling. I feel like fainting.
Thousands of thoughts are racing through my head.
I can control myself now but when we meet
I won't be able to utter a word.
I'll just stand still and stare at her.
Sorry, I need a drink.
Right next to the entrance. Can you hear me?
The entrance to where?
There's a white kiosk here. On your way from… What?
By the stairs?
Fuck, I don't see any stairs here.
You don't?
I don't. Wait. There's a sign over there. Jesus… What?
Are you by the Eiffel Tower now?
Yes. Let's meet right in the middle
beneath the Eiffel Tower, O.K.?
O.K. How are you dressed?
Dark brown trousers and a red-brown-white top.
I'm glad I've recorded this video-letter for her.
She'll have an opportunity to see me.
She'll meet Karolina, but she'll also see me.
I wonder what her reaction will be
when she sees me on tape.
Good morning. This is Bożena. Please, leave your message.
I've always wanted to have a mother.
I haven't had my mother for so many years
because you've been away. I hope it'll change now.
I don't want you to show up for 5 minutes
and then disappear for another 14 years.
I want you to stay with me for good.
Many people have told me that I look just like you.
The same height, same hair, same eyes.
We'll see if it’s true.