RABBITLAND
Rabbitland.
Nothing can change the wonderful impression.
Rabbits live in comfy pink homes.
Rabbits are happy.
And since they have no brains,
just holes in their heads
Nothing bad can happen to them.
They are the most perfect and highest stage in evolution.
Rabbits rise very early each morning,
put heavy blank sheets of paper
in the holes in their heads,
gather around the huge golden monument
and patiently wait for
the play button to be pressed.
And then, slowly and orderly, they start.
The journey is long
suprising
with many obstacles
IQ measuring points, but
despite that, the Rabbits travel slowly and dutifully,
with a clear goal.
They go far, far away,
up to the borders of Rabbitland,
even though beyond them there is nothing
but only empty areas, inhabited by
Evil Girls.
They go so far to vote at the elections,
which in Rabbitland take place once a day,
because it is a well-ordered democracy.
Remarkably easily,
one by one,
they insert the ballots
into a tall, tall ballot box.
The Evil Girls know that every vote is a vote for them.
The Rabbits return home full of joy.
And then, the Evil Girls press stop,
and the evening comes to Rabbitland.
The Rabbits go to sleep.
But, having no brain, they can't sleep.
so they watch the election results
on TV the whole night.
At the borders of Rabbitland, the Evil Girls play
and they laugh at another senseless day.
The Rabbits are happy.
Happy day in Rabbitland.
happy