THE DATE
They called from work, I have to go.
You need to take care of that date now.
Do I have to?
Yes you do. It's not a big deal,
you know the thrill.
It' Lissu from Oh Lala and that Mirka with Nefertiti,
I think you have met them.
Fine.
- Thanks honey. It'll be just fine.
Call me if there's something.
- Yeah, just go.
Hi!
Welcome.
Well hello Tino!
It's been a while since I saw you.
You're a grown man now.
There's some coat hangers there I think.
Hi.
- Hi.
Let's leave them to get to know each other.
Nefertiti has been screaming for three nights.
I'm really stressed about this all.
You always stress so much.
The nature takes it course.
I just got a letter.
Maserati, Nefertiti's half
sister from the father's side -
is a Quadruple Grand Champion.
Can you imagine, that little frog?
Nice. She is pretty.
How did Diablo do this season?
He got some rosettes.
Nefertiti is only flirting.
Some flirting.
She is screaming "Fuck me!"
"Now! Now! Right now!"
That sounds just like it is suppose to sound.
Good boy!
That was fast.
What is that fat ass stud doing to her?
Timing was just right, she was very willing.
Let's give Diablo a chance
to do his thing a couple of times.
That sounds just terrible.
I'm sorry I got so upset.
It's just that Neffi is so little
and it's her first time.
Diablo is a good stud.
He has never hurt any queens.
Are you sure?
Yeah. He's really experienced and patient.
She'll be ok.
I'm sure you right.
Yeah.
Thanks for the coffee and - for the stud.
That's ok.
Thanks, Tino.