Ahmad!
- How are you doing?
- What's up, Rafi?
How have you been? How's your health?
I brought you some hot coals.
Where have you been all week?
Sakhi saw me stealing from his shop,
so I had to hide out for a while.
How's work?
Not bad. But I have to get back — my father's waiting.
- Let's hang out today.
- There’s no way my dad will let me.
Oh, come on, take the day off.
Rafi! What are you doing?
I was getting water.
Get back to the shop.
I'll see you later.
Get out of here, bastard.
Let me bless you! My smoke cures the evil eye!
Quick! Get out your money!
May you become a mullah!
May you own three Corollas!
Mister, a blessing!
Uncle, let me bless you. Come on.
Just 5 or 10 rupees!
Come on, uncle!
What about you? Just one blessing!
I will pray that you get a better car!
Father, can I get some time off this afternoon?
Eat your food. We have work to do.
I'm full.
Clean up these plates, then.
Rafi, my son.
Yes?
You have two hours.
- I was about to leave without you.
- You wouldn't have done that.
All the best buzkashi riders will be competing.
You're going to love it.
Come on, hurry!
All aboard! Last stop, Sar-e-Kotal!
Look over there.
He's got the goat!
A buzkashi rider grabs the goat,
then they fight over it all the way to the flag.
Once the rider goes around the flag,
he takes the goat back to the circle.
That's how you score a point.
He's got it! He's got it!
Go! Go!
Look! He's bringing it back to the circle!
Come on!
He made it!
Attention all spectators!
They are as fast as deer, as focused as tigers ..
.. as quick as jackrabbits, and as fit as foxes!
All buzkashi riders in Afghanistan ..
.. from the North, from the South, from the West!
Cheer for these champions!
Look at that. I got one!
Lucky shot.
No more points for lucky shots.
At least I made it.
- I made it again! Was that one lucky?
- Of course.
That's how a real man throws it.
Don't get too excited over one shot.
I've made two to your one.
I'm still the champion, though.
You know what? One day I will be a buzkashi rider.
How are you going to do that?
You think I'm going to be on the streets forever?
You don't have a horse.
You need a horse to be a buzkashi rider.
Don't worry, I have a plan.
One day the announcer will call out my name
in front of everyone.
I'll be remembered as a buzkashi champion.
You have big dreams.
I know what my future will be.
I'm going to be a blacksmith like my father.
Nothing can change that.
You're wrong. You can do anything you want.
Come on. I want to show you something.
Whose palace was this?
Who cares?
I think it was some king.
Come on.
Where are we going?
Go ahead, climb up.
Go on.
I can't.
You always say that.
This is how you do it.
Ahmad, be careful, you'll fall.
Look, it's easy. Don't worry so much.
Forget it. I'm not doing it.
If you can't climb up here,
what kind of buzkashi rider will you be?
You'll be a blacksmith all your life.
My name is Ahmad, son of Abdullah!
And I will be a buzkashi rider!
I have to get back to the shop.
My father's waiting.
See you later.
Wait a minute.
What?
Oh, wow.
Where did you get this?
I got it from a buzkashi rider.
When did you meet a buzkashi rider?
Here, wear it like this.
This way your dad won't see it.
If you keep it with you all the time,
you'll be strong enough to ride buzkashi.
Now go.
Remember that you don't have to be a blacksmith.
Right.
See you tomorrow.
Goodbye.
Where were you?
You were with that fatherless beggar again, no?
Listen to me.
I want these sharp enough to shave with.
And you'll have no dinner tonight. Get started.
Rafi.
It's late. Go to sleep.
My grandfather was a blacksmith.
So was my father.
I was your age when I first picked up a hammer.
A blacksmith lives an honorable life.
Rafi.
What?
Come on, I want to show you something.
Okay.
Let's go.
So, are you a master blacksmith yet?
All I do is sharpen axe heads.
You think you can swing a hammer with those scrawny arms?
Laugh it up.
Where are we going?
Be patient. It's a surprise.
We're going up there.
Come on.
Hey there.
You're a beauty.
You're a real beauty.
Take this.
What are you doing?
Stop! What are you doing?,
Get down!
You said I needed a horse to ride buzkashi.
Now I have one!
Praise God the great and merciful ..
Let's go.
Take the hammer.
We need to shape the axe head. Hit it here.
What kind of hammering is that, boy?
Hit it like that.
You're not listening.
Like this.
Here, you do it.
What are you doing?
Is that how you hammer?
Son!
Rafi!
Ahmad!
Where were you, boy?
You said you would teach me.
Will you teach me now?
Good job.
Well done.